it's today's video I don't know if I've
talked about this yet but today's video
is going to be about what I would do if
I had one year left to live and I think
I did right do this video I'm her type
you know what you left to live but I'm
gonna do it again that's what I feel
called to do I was already doing one and
I ended up talking about it here the
last minute so I'm just going to talk
about it for this this minute so idea
that if we had a ton of money I had a
million dollars what would I spend it on
but the opposite is true for time it's
like what would I do with only a year
left to live and although I would spend
time with my child I would absolutely I
want to get this idea out there and so
I'm gonna spend the next year or less
it's not even a 90 day or 108 commitment
this is I need to write an hour a day
until this project is done until I've
finished this book that I feel at it
with adequately describes and explains
this global cooperative idea that I have
that I believe is the solution to most
of the world's problems and that we so
interconnected and complex that we need
to do it together and this is my
blueprint on how that looks because
people when they hear do it together is
like well how is that gonna work how
does this X happen or Y happen and
although I haven't solved a hundred
percent of it absolves probably 75 to
90% of it and the rest is up for us to
solve right like I don't have the energy
I don't have the answer for the energy
crisis but I guarantee you someone has
the answer that's already on this planet
it probably already has the answer and
doesn't know how to get it out there
doesn't know how to fight the powers
that be the energy corporations and we
need systems that are in place to help
people who have an idea that's going to
improve the world and want to gift it to
the world but even in the case of energy
if you don't want to necessarily gift it
you still won't have your your company
and profit from that I don't have an
issue with that but if the energy is
gonna save the world we need to know
that that technology exists we need to
know what it is and what it isn't what
the safety mechanisms are that are in
place to make sure it's safe and has it
been proven how much energy do we get
out of it what's the downside of it is
it better than what we got currently
going on because let's definitely
let's definitely do it that and so I'm
gonna be writing for an hour a day at
least four days a week I'm gonna take
the weekends off and possibly one day
during the week so four to five times a
week I will be writing for an hour just
sitting down and if I can do an outline
which doesn't seem I've been spending
months figure it out if I can do an
outline but just right now I'm just
gonna do stream-of-consciousness for an
hour about this idea and after that then
if an outline starts to materialize then
I'll have points that I need to sit down
write because I do really well writing
in these small chunks of time that are
that mimic a test-taking environment
that's how I wanted all of the writing
assignments university to be was a 1 was
it like a two-hour sitting and writing
because that's how I did all of my essay
is even my essays that we had months to
write come or weeks I don't know if we
had ever had another story and essay but
I would write it the day before and do
my research and everything that day and
that's how I work well on a timeline on
a deadline 10 line with a deadline
because they clearly thought would dwell
in a timeline then I would have would
have written over the course of weeks
but I write well with the deadline
looming when it's right there so if I do
that in small chunks of an hour at a
time I think I'm going to do better
writing but mainly it's just about
getting used to that that's sitting down
so I'll be doing my videos the hundred
of them for and so I'll be sharing that
process of explaining it through writing
as well as of course my life my life as
a person with a disability as a single
mom as a queer woman just discovering
that and that part of myself so sharing
that won't be in the writing I'm just
just talking about the global
cooperative in these videos and talking
about myself and my life and this
process of internal work that I need to
do in order to be who I need to be to be
comfortable giving this idea to the
world and the more uncomfortable in that
the easier it's gonna be and so that's
what these videos will be and
that's my commitment I also need to make
two videos this weekend to make up for
the two I didn't make this week or I'll
make another one later today but I want
to be at 25 videos by the ends of the
weekends so that I can start with 26 on
Monday thank you